<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hobby on vtsuki.net</title><link>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/tags/hobby/</link><description>Recent content in Hobby on vtsuki.net</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-GB</language><copyright>&amp;#169; 2006 - 2025 vtsuki.net</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://reverie89.github.io/sg/tags/hobby/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>vtsuki.net revamp</title><link>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2025-vtsuki-revamp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2025-vtsuki-revamp/</guid><description>&lt;p>vtsuki.net revamp use Hugo and AI prompt, now look super modern, got theme switch, mobile friendly, and everything automated. Japanese and Singlish content all AI generate, site host on GitHub Pages, jin satki!&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Use &lt;a href="https://gohugo.io">Hugo&lt;/a> to build site&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Use GitHub Copilot AI prompt to make site look nice&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Got light/dark theme&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Mobile responsive&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Theme custom until cannot recognize&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Japanese and Singlish content all AI generate&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Host on &lt;a href="https://github.com/reverie89/reverie89.github.io">GitHub Pages&lt;/a>, swee bo?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>IoT hydroponic watering system with ESP32</title><link>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2025-iot-hydroponic-watering-system-esp32/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2025-iot-hydroponic-watering-system-esp32/</guid><description>&lt;p>This project is automated hydroponic watering system using ESP32, smart enough to check water level before mixing nutrients. Use one 12V power supply for all pumps, convert voltage for microcontroller and sensors, very efficient for home hydroponics.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Automated watering system, no need manual&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Check water level before mix nutrients to right concentration&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Use single 12V power supply for water pump and peristaltic pumps, buck convert to 5V for microcontroller, 3.3V for sensors&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Docker image for VSCode Tunnel</title><link>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2024-docker-image-for-vscode-tunnel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2024-docker-image-for-vscode-tunnel/</guid><description>&lt;p>I make Docker image for VSCode Tunnel, can use Docker-in-Docker also. Got dev container support, image put on Docker Hub. GitHub got auto build, so update very easy. This project make remote dev workflow more shiok.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Run a tunnel for VSCode using Docker&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Supports Docker-in-Docker, which means support for dev containers&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Docker image published on &lt;a href="https://hub.docker.com/r/reverie89/vscode-tunnel">Docker Hub&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Published automated build on &lt;a href="https://github.com/reverie89/vscode-tunnel">GitHub&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Image Processor on the web</title><link>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2024-image-processor-web/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2024-image-processor-web/</guid><description>&lt;p>This web image processor let you upload jpg, png, gif, webp or zip, process everything online. Python backend do watermark, return file to you, never store on server. Got Docker, public can use and contribute.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Upload jpg, png, gif, webp or zip files, all can&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Python backend process image, return processed file, no save on server&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Can add image or text watermark, use your own font or mine, adjust opacity and position&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Code with help from ChatGPT 3.5&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Packaged with Docker, use &lt;a href="https://img.vtsuki.net">here&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Docker image on &lt;a href="https://hub.docker.com/r/reverie89/image-processor">Docker Hub&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Code on &lt;a href="https://github.com/reverie89/image-processor">GitHub&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Fix video preview duration lengths on Immich</title><link>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2024-fix-immich-video-preview-duration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2024-fix-immich-video-preview-duration/</guid><description>&lt;p>This project fix bug in Immich app, video preview duration not correct. Use AI and Python script to update sidecar files with correct duration, fix hundreds of records.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Immich is self-hosted photo and video backup app&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Got bug, video preview duration not display properly&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Reported in v1.91.4, still got problem in v1.93.3&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Only affect small number of users, but actually easy to fix, just tedious&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Use CodeGPT Plus to write Python script to fix&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Script go through folders, use ffprobe to get duration, update sidecar files (*.xmp)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Tested and updated 776 records, all ok&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Code on &lt;a href="https://github.com/reverie89/python-immich-fix-video-preview-time">GitHub&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Watermark images with Python via Docker</title><link>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2023-watermark-images-python-docker/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2023-watermark-images-python-docker/</guid><description>&lt;p>This project got Python program to batch watermark images, run inside Docker container, very portable. Support PNG, JPG, WEBP, can get from GitHub and Docker Hub, easy to use.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Python program overlay text at 45-degree angle (watermark) on image files (png, jpg, webp)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Batch process files from /input, output to /output, all auto one&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Wrap program in Docker container, can run anywhere&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Code on &lt;a href="https://github.com/reverie89/docker-python-watermark">GitHub&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Container image on &lt;a href="https://hub.docker.com/r/reverie89/python-watermark">Docker Hub&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Use Python 3.11, Pillow 9.0, Docker 23&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>RSVP check-in web app</title><link>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2020-rsvp-check-in/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2020-rsvp-check-in/</guid><description>&lt;p>Simple Python website for guest RSVP check-in, got CSV import/export and dashboard to track attendance. Make for event management, finish in two weeks chop chop.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Simple website with guest check-in system, no need headache&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Made in about 2 weeks using Python, fast and easy&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Docker image for Caddy (>300k pulls!)</title><link>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2020-docker-image-for-caddy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2020-docker-image-for-caddy/</guid><description>&lt;p>This project customize Docker image for Caddy web server, add authentication and DNS plugins, also disable telemetry. Make web server setup easy, got over 300,000 pulls wor.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Caddy is a lightweight open source web server, got auto HTTPS, and is written in Go&lt;/li>
&lt;li>I use its builder to add reauth (authentication) and cloudflare (DNS provider) plugins, and then hor disable telemetry&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Docker container available on Docker Hub so anyone can use. Good right?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>vtsuki.net migration to Docker setup</title><link>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2019-vtsuki-net-migration-to-docker-setup/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2019-vtsuki-net-migration-to-docker-setup/</guid><description>&lt;p>This project migrate vtsuki.net to Docker, split services across VPS, use HTTPS and Cloudflare for security. Optimize Storage and memory lah. Internal services all run inside Docker network so it only expose what I need. Add personal profile to site, make web services more reliable, secure, and easier to maintain.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Add one more VPS, one for web server, one for Docker play play&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Mount extra storage to VPS #2&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Create swapfile for more memory, no need pay for extra RAM, save cost&lt;/li>
&lt;li>All web services use HTTPS with LetsEncrypt, auto renew, DNS go through Cloudflare&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Services not meant for internet make them run within Docker network only, use Caddy to reverse proxy everything&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Created a personalised webpage on vtsuki.net&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>GTA-V portblock</title><link>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2018-gtav-portblock/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2018-gtav-portblock/</guid><description>&lt;p>This project make batch file to manage Windows Firewall for GTA-V, can block ports and whitelist IPv4 addresses, so can play private online session without modding the game.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Create bat file to make it easy to block ports and whitelist IPv4 for GTA-V on PC&lt;/li>
&lt;li>CEO missions and Biker business need online session, but sometimes got cheaters, want to play peacefully&lt;/li>
&lt;li>No need to mod the game, just block some outbound traffic, only allow certain IPv4 (like your friend) to join your private session&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://github.com/reverie89/gtav-portblock">GitHub repo&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Contribute to GitHub repo</title><link>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2014-contribute-github-repo/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2014-contribute-github-repo/</guid><description>&lt;p>I go fix bug for LinuxGSM, help GameServerManagers lah. Now server more steady, no anyhow crash. My contribution got record in the commit link. This one show I know how to work with open source people.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Did a bugfix for &lt;a href="https://github.com/reverie89/linuxgameservers/commit/afb3f89d8ac5fc1f02458798eaeea876491484bb">GameServerManagers/LinuxGSM&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Game forum</title><link>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2013-game-forum/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2013-game-forum/</guid><description>&lt;p>This project try to setup game forum and all the backend, but stop halfway because not worth the effort.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Forum for games like Natural Selection 2, Team Fortress 2, even plan to host private game server, but too busy, never maintain, website also not much people visit&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Buy domain name, host forum on my VPS, connect domain to Outlook email, do all the server admin and firewall, everything ownself settle&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Launch of vtsuki.net</title><link>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2006-launch-vtsuki-net/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2006-launch-vtsuki-net/</guid><description>&lt;p>This one is my hobby project, launch vtsuki.net with Flash animation, got interactive features and portfolio page, quite shiok.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Try to make vtsuki.net website using old school Macromedia Flash and ActionScript&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Got animated loading bar when open index to look pro&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Bottom is real-time clock, opening got background sound (about 4 seconds), top menu all clickable links, can navigate around one&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Evo-ViRz.net experimental website</title><link>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2005-evovirz-experimental-website/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2005-evovirz-experimental-website/</guid><description>&lt;p>This one is my hobby project, just wanna try PHP and web design, play around with custom images and use table for layout, old school style lah.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>First time try PHP coding, blur like sotong but learn fast. Use GIMP to make the images, not bad hor. Layout all use table tag, last time like that one.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item></channel></rss>