<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>JET on vtsuki.net</title><link>https://reverie89.github.io/tags/jet/</link><description>Recent content in JET on vtsuki.net</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-GB</language><copyright>&amp;#169; 2006 - 2025 vtsuki.net</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://reverie89.github.io/tags/jet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>JET Opinion Exchange Conference</title><link>https://reverie89.github.io/pastworks/2015-jet-opinion-exchange-conference/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reverie89.github.io/pastworks/2015-jet-opinion-exchange-conference/</guid><description>&lt;p>This conference provided a platform for JET participants to share experiences and propose improvements. As a Singapore representative, I contributed to discussions on key issues and actionable solutions for the community.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Attended a CLAIR conference&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Voiced opinions on the issues experienced by JET participants as a Singapore representative&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Discussed potential improvements and actions to undertake&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>JET Japanese Tea Ceremony Experiential Class</title><link>https://reverie89.github.io/pastworks/2015-jet-tea/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reverie89.github.io/pastworks/2015-jet-tea/</guid><description>&lt;p>This experiential class introduced the Japanese Tea Ceremony to foreign residents and helped Japanese residents learn English vocabulary for cultural exchange, culminating in a shared appreciation event.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Introduction of Japanese Tea Ceremony to foreign residents of Miyazaki City&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Teach Japanese residents specific English vocabulary used for conversations on Japanese Tea Ceremony over a course of 3 sessions&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The Japanese residents will then use the 4th session introduce to the foreign residents how to appreciate Japanese Tea Ceremony&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>JET Introduce Singapore</title><link>https://reverie89.github.io/pastworks/2015-jet-introduce-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reverie89.github.io/pastworks/2015-jet-introduce-singapore/</guid><description>&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Introduce Singapore and its culture to Takaoka Town of Miyazaki Prefecture&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>This project involved presenting Singapore&amp;rsquo;s culture to residents of Takaoka Town, Miyazaki, fostering cross-cultural understanding and appreciation.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>JET Singapore Chicken Rice Cooking Class</title><link>https://reverie89.github.io/pastworks/2015-jet-cooking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reverie89.github.io/pastworks/2015-jet-cooking/</guid><description>&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Cooking class for Miyazaki City residents introducing Singapore&amp;rsquo;s signature food&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>A cooking class was held to introduce Singapore&amp;rsquo;s iconic Chicken Rice to Miyazaki City residents, promoting culinary exchange and cultural appreciation.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>JET Christmas Market Event</title><link>https://reverie89.github.io/pastworks/2014-jet-christmas-market-event/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reverie89.github.io/pastworks/2014-jet-christmas-market-event/</guid><description>&lt;p>This event brought together foreign residents of Miyazaki to volunteer and celebrate at the Christmas Market, fostering community spirit and cultural exchange.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Event was originally started by my predecessor&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Recruited foreign residents of Miyazaki to volunteer and participate as Santas and Santarinas in the event&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Assisted in purchase of materials e.g. non-bake cake making ingredients for use at the event&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Participated in the event as a foreign resident of Miyazaki City&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item></channel></rss>