<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>JET on vtsuki.net</title><link>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/tags/jet/</link><description>Recent content in JET on vtsuki.net</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-GB</language><copyright>&amp;#169; 2006 - 2025 vtsuki.net</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://reverie89.github.io/sg/tags/jet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>JET Opinion Exchange Conference</title><link>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2015-jet-opinion-exchange-conference/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2015-jet-opinion-exchange-conference/</guid><description>&lt;p>This conference is for JET people to share experience and suggest improvements. I go as Singapore rep, join the discussion, talk about important issues and what can do better for the community.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Attend CLAIR conference, meet other JETs&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Speak up about problems JET participants face, represent Singapore side&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Discuss how to improve and what action to take, all for the community&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>JET Japanese Tea Ceremony Experiential Class</title><link>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2015-jet-tea/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2015-jet-tea/</guid><description>&lt;p>This class purpose is to introduce Japanese Tea Ceremony to foreign residents, also teach Japanese residents some English words for their Japanese tea ceremony, so that foreign residents can come appreciate Japanese culture.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Introduce Japanese Tea Ceremony to foreign residents in Miyazaki City&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Teach Japanese residents in 3 sessions some basic English words about Japanese tea ceremony&lt;/li>
&lt;li>At the Tea Ceremony, the Japanese students showed foreign residents how to appreciate tea ceremony, all enjoy together&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>JET Introduce Singapore</title><link>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2015-jet-introduce-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2015-jet-introduce-singapore/</guid><description>&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Introduce Singapore and its culture to Takaoka Town, Miyazaki Prefecture&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>This project go and present Singapore culture to Takaoka Town people, let them know more about us, promote cross-cultural understanding, make everyone happy.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>JET Singapore Chicken Rice Cooking Class</title><link>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2015-jet-cooking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2015-jet-cooking/</guid><description>&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Cooking class for Miyazaki City residents, show them how to make Singapore&amp;rsquo;s famous food&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Hold cooking class to teach Miyazaki people how to make Singapore Chicken Rice, exchange cultures and let everyone try shiok foods.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>JET Christmas Market Event</title><link>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2014-jet-christmas-market-event/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://reverie89.github.io/sg/pastworks/2014-jet-christmas-market-event/</guid><description>&lt;p>This event bring all the foreign residents in Miyazaki together, volunteer and celebrate at Christmas Market, got community spirit and cultural exchange, very happening.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Event actually started by my predecessor not me, I just continue the tradition&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Recruit foreign residents to be Santas and Santarinas, everyone join in the fun&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Help buy materials like non-bake cake ingredients for the event, all settle&lt;/li>
&lt;li>I also join as foreign resident, enjoy the event together&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item></channel></rss>